https://grapentin.com/customer-service/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Need Help?
Password *
Lost password ?
Privacy Statement
Need Help?
MENU BOTTOM ROW
Have Questions or need something you can't find...  Call us at 810-724-0636!
Your Privacy Rights
This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, storage, sharing and protection of your personal information.  You accept this Privacy Policy when you sign up for, access, or use our products, services, content, features, technologies or functions offered on our website. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website.
How we collection information about you
When you visit the Grapentin.com website, we collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone or other access device. The information sent to us includes data on the pages you access, your computer IP address, device identifiers, the type of operating system you’re using, your location, mobile network information, standard web log data and other information. Web log data includes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from our site.  When you place an order through Grapentin or subscribe to our newsletters, we may collect the following types of information: Contact information, such as your name, address, phone, email and other similar information. Financial information, such as the full bank account numbers and/or credit card numbers used to process you order.
How we use Cookies
When you access our website, we may place small data files on your computer or other device. These data files may be cookies, pixel tags, “Flash cookies” or other local storage provided by your browser or associated applications (“Cookies”). We use these technologies to: recognize you as a customer; customize content, and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness; help ensure that your account security is not compromised; mitigate risk and prevent fraud; and to promote trust and safety on the Grapentin.com website. We use both session and persistent Cookies. Session Cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent Cookies remain on your device until you erase them or they expire. We encode our Cookies so that we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our Cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website and the ability to process your order.
How we protect and store personal information
Throughout this policy, we use the term “personal information” to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous so that it does not identify a specific user. We protect your information using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls.
How we use the personal information we collect
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Your information will on be used to process orders placed on the Grapentin.com website or by phone to Grapentin Specialties.
Our assurance to you
We make every attempt possible to ensure the privacy of our customers personal and credit information. When you submit your order, you will be utilizing a SSL (Secure Socket Layer).  All information is transmitted on a secure “layer”, shown by the letters “http” at the beginning of the Website URL.  This secure measure is also shown by the lock icon displayed in the browser. The use of the SSL is the safest and most secure method of transferring confidential informatinon the Internet today.  SSL will scramble (encrypt) the infromation sent from your computer to the Website server.  When the site administrator retrieves your order, only they have the ability to descramble (decrypt) the credit card information. Under no circumstance, unless court ordered, will we every provide customer information to a third party.
Disclaimer:
Although every possible method is taken to ensure information security, nothing on the Internet is 100% secure.  If at any time we find that any Grapentin customer data has been comprimised, all customers will be contacted immediately in writing and/or by phone.
As such, when placing an order on Grapentin.com either online or by phone, the customer accepts these privacy statements and acknowledges that Grapentin.com or it’s Website Administrator can not be held responsible for any given Website failure or comprimised client information and data that occurs after all possible security measures have been put in place and thus Grapentin.com Customer agrees to not hold Grapentin Specialties or it’s Website Administrator responsible or liable for any incidental or consequential costs and or damages that may occur.  Customer assumes full responsibility for Website use, including providing customer credit card and personal information.
Copyright ©2017-2019 Grapentin.com. All rights reserved.   |   Sitemap
Web Design & Development by: Abke Design
×
SIGN UP TODAY FOR A10% OFF COUPONPLUS
BE THE FIRST TO KNOW ABOUT SALES & SPECIALS
Email address:
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Don’t worry, we won’t spam our customers mailboxes.
